Guide to the Collins Land Company (Helena, Mont.) Records 1898-1951
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Case Files, 1907-1951; Series II; 28.5 linear feet
  - Sequence 1, Subseries 1; 7.5 linear feet
    - Connors, James A., Petaluma, California, Case Number 1854 (Box-folder 34/6)
    - Langley, William H., Petaluma, California, Case Number 1855 (Box-folder 34/7)
    - Moulton, C. E., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 1856 (Box-folder 34/8)
    - Moulton, C. E., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 1856 (Box-folder 34/9)
    - Selby, Jacob S., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 1883 (Box-folder 34/10)
    - Grable, Henry H., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 1885 (Box-folder 34/11)
    - Thisted, Fred A., Stark, Montana, Case Number 2058 (Box-folder 35/1)
    - Stewart, J. R., Minneapolis, Minnesota, Case Number 2129 (Box-folder 35/2)
    - Beal, Dr. Wilbur L., Anaconda, Montana, Case Number 2140 (Box-folder 35/3)
    - Northern Pacific Scrip, Anaconda, Montana, Case Number 2253 (Box-folder 35/4)
    - Northern Pacific Scrip, Anaconda, Montana, Case Number 2253A (Box-folder 35/5)
    - Espanda Company, Buffalo, Wyoming, Case Number 2305 (Box-folder 35/6)
    - Wisconsin Michigan Power Company, Appleton, Wisconsin, Case Number 2362 (Box-folder 35/7)
    - Denning and Clark, Dubois, Idaho, Case Number 2373 (Box-folder 35/8)
    - Denning and Clark, Dubois, Idaho, Case Number 2373 (Box-folder 35/9)
    - Sherman, E. H., Helena, Montana, Case Number 2382 (Box-folder 35/10)
    - Howes, Levi S., Otter, Montana, Case Number 2568 (Box-folder 35/11)
    - Henderson, George, West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2624 (Box-folder 35/12)
    - Wilson, John H., West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2625 (Box-folder 35/13)
    - Bell, Charles E., Ogden, Utah, Case Number 2626 (Box-folder 35/14)
    - Stewart, Alexander L., West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2627 (Box-folder 35/15)
    - Garner, Kirby, West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2633 (Box-folder 35/16)
    - Pierman, Jesse E., West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2634 (Box-folder 35/17)
    - White, Joseph E., West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2635 (Box-folder 36/1)
    - Murray, Mabel E., West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2636 (Box-folder 36/2)
    - Bartlett, Dolly, West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2637 (Box-folder 36/3)
    - Bucy, Monroe W., West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2638 (Box-folder 36/4)
    - Murray, Lebbeus A., West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2639 (Box-folder 36/5)
    - Bucy, Clarence, West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2640 (Box-folder 36/6)
    - Streider, Dorothy M., West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2641 (Box-folder 36/7)
    - Lane, Clarence E., West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2642 (Box-folder 36/8)
    - Hurless, Samuel F., West Yellowstone, Montana, Case Number 2643 (Box-folder 36/9)
    - Pigott, Harry H., Helena, Montana, Case Number 2651 (Box-folder 36/10)
    - Barker Wilson Company, Butte, TAT, Case Number 2721 (Box-folder 36/11)
    - Hazelbaker, Frank A., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 2725 (Box-folder 36/12)
    - Robertson, Juneau, Alaska (R.E.), Case Number 2778 (Box-folder 36/13)
    - Thomas E. Brady Estate, Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 2784 (Box-folder 36/14)
    - Robertson, R. E., Juneau, Alaska, Case Number 2813 (Box-folder 36/15)
    - The Dubois Abstract Company, Dubois, Idaho, Case Number 2817 (Box-folder 36/16)
    - Funnemark, Benjamin A. J., Culdesac, Idaho, Case Number 2838 (Box-folder 36/17)
    - Anaconda Copper Mining Company, Charles H. Niblack, Case Number 2840 (Box-folder 36/18)
    - Montana Power Company, Butte, Montana, Case Number 2856 (Box-folder 36/19)
    - Pennington, W. W., Butte, Montana, Case Number 2867 (Box-folder 37/1)
    - Haines, Roscoe, Missoula, Montana, Case Number 2873 (Box-folder 37/2)
    - Baker, Dr. E. D., Spokane, Washington, Case Number 2876 (Box-folder 37/3)
    - The Swan Company, Chugwater, Wyoming, Case Number 2894 (Box-folder 37/4)
    - Eighorn Stock Company, Butte, Montana, Case Number 2929 (Box-folder 37/5)
    - Trace, Orlando F., St. Paul, Minnesota, Case Number 3002 (Box-folder 37/6)
    - Trace, Orlando F., St. Paul, Minnesota, Case Number 3002 (Box-folder 37/7)
    - Wentz, Walter Y., San Diego, California, Case Number 3098 (Box-folder 37/8)
    - Wentz, Walter Y., San Diego, California, Case Number 3098 (Box-folder 37/9)
    - Thomas, Lorenzo R., Blackfoot, Idaho, Case Number 3196 (Box-folder 37/10)
  - Sequence 2, Subseries 2; 9.0 linear feet
    - Teton Cooperative Reservoir Company, Case Number 5 (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Teton Cooperative Reservoir Company, Case Number 5 (Box-folder 38/2)
    - Teton Cooperative Reservoir Company, Case Number 5 (Box-folder 38/3)
    - Teton Cooperative Reservoir Company, Case Number 5 (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Teton Cooperative Reservoir Company, Case Number 5 (Box-folder 38/5)
    - Teton Cooperative Reservoir Company, Case Number 5 (Box-folder 38/6)
    - Cruse, Thomas, Case Number 46 (Box-folder 38/7)
    - Lepper, Benjamin F., Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 60 (Box-folder 38/8)
    - Gesche, Adolph L., Case Number 63 (Box-folder 38/9)
    - Northwestern Livestock Company, Case Number 64 (Box-folder 38/10)
    - Milner Cattle Company, Case Number 103 (Box-folder 39/1)
    - McLaughlin, W. W., Case Number 138 (Box-folder 39/2)
    - Burke, John H., Case Number 143 (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Power, Charles B., Helena, Montana, Case Number 156 (Box-folder 39/4)
    - Burke, John H., Hogan, Montana, Case Number 166 (Box-folder 39/5)
    - Burke, John H., Hogan, Montana, Case Number 167 (Box-folder 39/6)
    - Burke, John H., Hogan, Montana, Case Number 168 (Box-folder 39/7)
    - Burke, John H., Hogan, Montana, Case Number 169 (Box-folder 39/8)
    - Osnes, Ole C., Knerville, Montana, Case Number 177 (Box-folder 39/9)
    - Power, Charles B., Helena, Montana, Case Number 178 (Box-folder 39/10)
    - Burlingame, J. M., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 179 (Box-folder 39/11)
    - Matz, W. S., Sheridan, Wyoming, Case Number 180 (Box-folder 39/12)
    - Rhodes, W. E., Glasgow, Montana, Case Number 181 (Box-folder 39/13)
    - Gilbert, John R., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 182 (Box-folder 39/14)
    - Big Sag Land and Livestock Company, Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 183 (Box-folder 39/15)
    - Wight, Alex, Hall, Montana, Case Number 185 (Box-folder 39/16)
    - Moulton, C. E., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 188 (Box-folder 39/17)
    - Howes, Levi S., Otter, Montana, Case Number 189 (Box-folder 39/18)
    - Eccles, Robert, Gillette, Wyoming, Case Number 191 (Box-folder 40/1)
    - Eccles, Robert, Gillette, Wyoming, Case Number 192 (Box-folder 40/2)
    - Eccles, Robert, Gillette, Wyoming, Case Number 196 (Box-folder 40/3)
    - Osnes, Ole G., Knerville, Montana, Case Number 209 (Box-folder 40/4)
    - Howes, Augustus, Hood River, Oregon, Case Number 213 (Box-folder 40/5)
    - Bolen, E. B., Froid, Montana, Case Number 214 (Box-folder 40/6)
    - Lohse, Hartwig, Judith, Montana, Case Number 215 (Box-folder 40/7)
    - Day-Hansen Security Company, Spokane, Washington, Case Number 216 (Box-folder 40/8)
    - Frary, W. S., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 218 (Box-folder 40/9)
    - Hammond, Thomas E., Forsyth, Montana, Case Number 219 (Box-folder 40/10)
    - Selway, Robert W., Sheridan, Wyoming, Case Number 220 (Box-folder 40/11)
    - Northern Lumber Company, New York City, New York, Case Number 223 (Box-folder 41/1)
    - Horkan, George, Miles City, Montana, Case Number 227 (Box-folder 41/2)
    - Godfrey, Nathan, Helena, Montana, and Hensen, William R., Chinook, Montana, Case Number 238 (Box-folder 41/3)
    - Clark, W. A., Butte, Montana, Case Number 242 (Box-folder 41/4)
    - Libby, Charles E. and Merrill, C. H., Conrad, Montana, Case Number 245 (Box-folder 41/5)
    - Reed, Oliver, Miles City, Montana, Case Number 246 (Box-folder 41/6)
    - Partridge, George L., Malta, Montana, Case Number 247 (Box-folder 41/7)
    - Scott, Joseph, Miles City, Montana, Case Number 248 (Box-folder 41/8)
    - Nutter, Preston, Tucker, Utah, Case Number 253 (Box-folder 41/9)
    - Wetmore, Ira P., Roswell, New Mexico, Case Number 254 (Box-folder 41/10)
    - Hammond, Thomas E., Roswell, New Mexico, Case Number 255 (Box-folder 41/11)
    - O'Connor, John E., Canton, Montana, Case Number 256 (Box-folder 41/12)
    - Wood Livestock Company, Spencer, Idaho, Case Number 258 (Box-folder 41/13)
    - Murray, James P., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 260 (Box-folder 41/14)
    - McKay, Daniel, Miles City, Montana, Case Number 262 (Box-folder 41/15)
    - Harris, W. E., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 263 (Box-folder 41/16)
    - Cornwell, Robert L., Glasgow, Montana, Case Number 265 (Box-folder 41/17)
    - Devlin, L. K., Havre, Montana, Case Number 269 (Box-folder 41/18)
    - Sayre, Edgar, Martinsdale, Montana, Case Number 275 (Box-folder 41/19)
    - Cook, Stephan, Lima, Montana, Case Number 278 (Box-folder 42/1)
    - Brown, Joseph T., Birney, Montana, Case Number 280 (Box-folder 42/2)
    - Kelsey, Samuel W., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 301 (Box-folder 42/3)
    - Barrett, Martin, Dillon, Montana, Case Number 308 (Box-folder 42/4)
    - Harris, John, Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 319 (Box-folder 42/5)
    - Lindstrand, Carl, Flat Willow, Montana, Case Number 320 (Box-folder 42/6)
    - Snead, Thomas E., Hinsdale, Montana, Case Number 324 (Box-folder 42/7)
    - Harris, W. E., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 326 (Box-folder 42/8)
    - Smith George J., Choteau, Montana, Case Number 327 (Box-folder 42/9)
    - Strong, William G., Helena, Montana, Case Number 328 (Box-folder 42/10)
    - Bannatyne, Charles, Collins, Montana, Case Number 329 (Box-folder 42/11)
    - Thompson, Robert, Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 351 (Box-folder 42/12)
    - Phelps, L. G., Meeteetse, Wyoming, Case Number 358 (Box-folder 42/13)
    - Davenport, William, Helena, Montana, Case Number 359 (Box-folder 42/14)
    - Craver, Mary D., Red Rock, Montana, Case Number 361 (Box-folder 42/15)
    - Luppold, William, White Sulphur Springs, Montana, Case Number 364 (Box-folder 42/16)
    - Cobban, R. M., Missoula, Montana, Case Number 377 (Box-folder 42/17)
    - Elderman, Andrew, Big Sandy, Montana, Case Number 378 (Box-folder 42/18)
    - Jacobson and Reip, Chester, Montana, Case Number 379 (Box-folder 43/1)
    - Knight, M. P., Butte, Montana, Case Number 380 (Box-folder 43/2)
    - Strode, Thomas P., Whitlash, Montana, Case Number 381 (Box-folder 43/3)
    - Wallace, William J., Whitlash, Montana, Case Number 383 (Box-folder 43/4)
    - Hill, H. B., Mondak, Montana, Case Number 385 (Box-folder 43/5)
    - Falxa, John, Plentywood, Montana, Case Number 386 (Box-folder 43/6)
    - Brassey and Shafer, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 387 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - Jones-Edward, Conrad, Montana, Case Number 389 (Box-folder 43/8)
    - Hensen, Carl F., Zortman, Montana, Case Number 390 (Box-folder 43/9)
    - McReynolds, F. W., Washington, D.C., Case Number 391 (Box-folder 43/10)
    - Sullivan, Jere, Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 392 (Box-folder 43/11)
    - Nolan, Joseph P., Butte, Montana, Case Number 393 (Box-folder 43/12)
    - Rhodes, W. E, Glasgow, Montana, Case Number 394 (Box-folder 43/13)
    - Brassey and Stack, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 395 (Box-folder 43/14)
    - Browne, F. S., Camas Valley, Oregon, Case Number 396 (Box-folder 43/15)
    - Hartt, D. N., Helena, Montana, Case Number 397 (Box-folder 44/1)
    - Johnson and Boone, Dillon, Montana, Case Number 398 (Box-folder 44/2)
    - Craver, T. B., Armstead, Montana, Case Number 400 (Box-folder 44/3)
    - Tovey, D. W., Malad, Idaho, Case Number 401 (Box-folder 44/4)
    - Prescott, A. K., Helena, Montana, Case Number 402 (Box-folder 44/5)
    - William-Hill Company, Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 403 (Box-folder 44/6)
    - Frary, W. S., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 404 (Box-folder 44/7)
    - Tabor, N. G., Corchester, Wisconsin, Case Number 405 (Box-folder 44/8)
    - Swenson, J. A., Kirby, Wyoming, Case Number 407 (Box-folder 44/9)
    - Fowler, A. J., Shelby, Montana, Case Number 409 (Box-folder 44/10)
    - Donlan, Edward, Missoula, Montana, Case Number 411 (Box-folder 44/11)
    - Johnston, James L., White Sulphur Springs, Case Number 412 (Box-folder 44/12)
    - Manley, John E., Drummond, Montana, Case Number 413 (Box-folder 44/13)
    - Fogarty, Edmond, Sand Cliffs, Montana, Case Number 414 (Box-folder 44/14)
    - Hill, H. B., Mondak, Montana, Case Number 415 (Box-folder 44/15)
    - Frary, W. S,. Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 416 (Box-folder 44/16)
    - Newhall, E. B., Big Sandy, Montana, Case Number 417 (Box-folder 44/17)
    - Wallace, William J., Whitlash, Montana, Case Number 418 (Box-folder 44/18)
    - Bickett-Sweet Livestock Company, Helena, Montana, Case Number 423 (Box-folder 45/1)
    - Frary, W. S., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 426 (Box-folder 45/2)
    - Wood Livestock Company, Spencer, Idaho, Case Number 434 (Box-folder 45/3)
    - Van Horn, C. W., Crabtree, Montana, Case Number 443 (Box-folder 45/4)
    - Clark, Julian C., Sweetgrass, Montana, Case Number 448 (Box-folder 45/5)
    - Anderson, Hans, Ketchikan, Alaska, Case Number 450 (Box-folder 45/6)
    - Nolan, Joseph P., Butte, Montana, Case Number 456 (Box-folder 45/7)
    - Kelley, Edward B., Finn, Montana, Case Number 459 (Box-folder 45/8)
    - Heywood, Arthur P., Helena, Montana, Case Number 462 (Box-folder 45/9)
    - American Livestock and Loan Company, Denver, Colorado, Case Number 463 (Box-folder 45/10)
    - Skillman, C. N., Big Timber, Montana, Case Number 468 (Box-folder 45/11)
    - Potter, Samuel L., Shelby, Montana, Case Number 471 (Box-folder 45/12)
    - Knapp, Henry F., Collins, Montana, Case Number 472 (Box-folder 45/13)
    - Citizens State Bank, Choteau, Montana, Case Number 475 (Box-folder 45/14)
    - Mills, Lincoln H., Saco, Montana, Case Number 478 (Box-folder 45/15)
    - Bruegger, Jacob I., Culbertson, Montana, Case Number 491 (Box-folder 45/16)
    - Power, C. B., Helena, Montana, Case Number 496 (Box-folder 45/17)
    - Norton and Lyons, Big Elk, Montana, Case Number 518 (Box-folder 45/18)
    - Waring, L. C., Decatur, Indiana, Case Number 525 (Box-folder 46/1)
    - Schmidt Brothers and Greely, Fort Benton, Case Number 533 (Box-folder 46/2)
    - Prescott, A. K., Helena, Montana, Case Number 547 (Box-folder 46/3)
    - Boone, R. W., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 549 (Box-folder 46/4)
    - Jones, John W., Blackfoot, Idaho, Case Number 557 (Box-folder 46/5)
    - Freeman, George O., Helena, Montana, Case Number 573 (Box-folder 46/6)
    - Blake, Edward W., Helena, Montana, Case Number 585 (Box-folder 46/7)
    - Lawlor and Rowe, Butte, Montana, Case Number 598 (Box-folder 46/8)
    - Jones, John W., Blackfoot, Idaho, Case Number 599 (Box-folder 46/9)
    - Manley, John E., Drummond, Montana, Case Number 609 (Box-folder 46/10)
    - Brown, Walter, Box Elder, Montana, Case Number 621 (Box-folder 46/11)
    - Helena Farms Company, Helena, Montana, Case Number 627 (Box-folder 46/12)
    - Selway, Robert R., Sheridan, Wyoming, Case Number 633 (Box-folder 46/13)
    - Daly, James H., Franklin, Montana, Case Number 638 (Box-folder 46/14)
    - Osnes, Ole G., Knerville, Montana, Case Number 640 (Box-folder 46/15)
    - Crowley, Tena, Ulm, Montana, Case Number 664 (Box-folder 46/16)
    - Devlin, L. K., Havre, Montana, Case Number 665 (Box-folder 46/17)
    - Brown, William H., Havre, Montana, Case Number 667 (Box-folder 47/1)
    - Redwing, Edward, Havre, Montana, Case Number 674 (Box-folder 47/2)
    - Moulton, C. E., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 686 (Box-folder 47/3)
    - Baley and Baley, Pendleton, Oregon, Case Number 692 (Box-folder 47/4)
    - Randall, J. B., Wolf Point, Montana, Case Number 699 (Box-folder 47/5)
    - Atkins, Mrs. Julia E., Missoula, Montana, Case Number 747 (Box-folder 47/6)
    - Barker-Wilson Company, Butte, Montana, Case Number 761 (Box-folder 47/7)
    - Rexburg State Bank, Rexburg, Idaho, Case Number 772 (Box-folder 47/8)
    - Murphy, Homer G., Helena, Montana, Case Number 776 (Box-folder 47/9)
    - Patterson, Judge C. C., Heppner, Oregon, Case Number 780 (Box-folder 47/10)
    - Hobson, S. S., Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 782 (Box-folder 47/11)
    - Laughlin, Gertrude E., Ovando, Montana, Case Number 785 (Box-folder 47/12)
    - Barker-Wilson Company, Butte, Montana, Case Number 788 (Box-folder 47/13)
    - Orr, William C., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 789 (Box-folder 47/14)
    - Marlow, Thomas A., Helena, Montana, Case Number 803 (Box-folder 47/15)
    - Ruby Gulch Mining Company, Zortman, Montana, Case Number 805 (Box-folder 47/16)
    - Ball, W. M., Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 809 (Box-folder 47/17)
    - Fennell, W. P., Washington, D.C., Case Number 817 (Box-folder 47/18)
    - Lannen, Chris, Bearmouth, Montana, Case Number 822 (Box-folder 47/19)
    - Hilger, David, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 827 (Box-folder 48/1)
    - Jones, Edward, Conrad, Montana, Case Number 828 (Box-folder 48/2)
    - Sawyer, Leicester J., Tibbals, Florida, Case Number 829 (Box-folder 48/3)
    - Seattle National Bank, Seattle, Washington, Case Number 836 (Box-folder 48/4)
    - O'Neil, Martin, Havre, Montana, Case Number 841 (Box-folder 48/5)
    - Brock, A. M., Buffalo, Wyoming, Case Number 850 (Box-folder 48/6)
    - Sanders, John D., Augusta, Montana, Case Number 851 (Box-folder 48/7)
    - Barnes, Lyman, Malta, Montana, Case Number 852 (Box-folder 48/8)
    - Fulton, William, Teedee, Montana, Case Number 855 (Box-folder 48/9)
    - Trenam, A. L., Weiser, Idaho, Case Number 856 (Box-folder 48/10)
    - Sprinkle, James L., Chinook, Montana, Case Number 860 (Box-folder 48/11)
    - W. E. Moses Land Scrip and Realty, Denver, Colorado, Case Number 867 (Box-folder 48/12)
    - Moulton, C. E., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 868 (Box-folder 48/13)
    - Horkan, George, Miles City, Montana, Case Number 878 (Box-folder 48/14)
    - Day and Hansen Security Company, Spokane, Washington, Case Number 881 (Box-folder 48/15)
    - Power, Charles B., Helena, Montana, Case Number 887 (Box-folder 48/16)
    - McGahon, John, Valier, Montana, Case Number 889 (Box-folder 49/1)
    - Hedges, Henry H., Saco, Montana, Case Number 902 (Box-folder 49/2)
    - Elliot, Alexander, Malta, Montana, Case Number 904 (Box-folder 49/3)
    - Hilger, David, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 907 (Box-folder 49/4)
    - Thomson, James; Simpson, William L., Cody, Wyoming, Case Number 911 (Box-folder 49/5)
    - Sands, W. B., Chinook, Montana, Case Number 914 (Box-folder 49/6)
    - Baum, Raimund, Winston, Montana, Case Number 917 (Box-folder 49/7)
    - Baum, Raimund, Winston, Montana, Case Number 918 (Box-folder 49/8)
    - Barnes, B. B., Challis, Idaho, Case Number 919 (Box-folder 49/9)
    - Kremer, Harry D., Bozeman, Montana, Case Number 920 (Box-folder 49/10)
    - Smith, Pearl I., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 921 (Box-folder 49/11)
    - Belgrade State Bank, Belgrade, Montana, Case Number 925 (Box-folder 49/12)
    - Howes, Levi S., Otter, Montana, Case Number 926 (Box-folder 49/13)
    - Henry, Charles F., Townsend, Montana, Case Number 928 (Box-folder 49/14)
    - Boone, R. W., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 939 (Box-folder 49/15)
    - Chandler, John, Musselshell, Montana, Case Number 940 (Box-folder 49/16)
    - Kester, Bruce R., Vale, Oregon, Case Number 954 (Box-folder 49/17)
    - Mammen, J. H., Conanche, Montana, Case Number 956 (Box-folder 49/18)
    - Bear Tooth Stock Company, Helena, Montana, Case Number 958 (Box-folder 49/19)
    - McConnell, A. H., St. Anthony, Idaho, Case Number 959 (Box-folder 49/20)
    - Fogarty, Edmond, Sand Cliffs, Montana, Case Number 962 (Box-folder 49/21)
    - Grande, A. C., Lennup, Montana, Case Number 967 (Box-folder 49/22)
    - Henry, Charles F., Townsend, Montana, Case Number 972 (Box-folder 49/23)
    - Kimpton, Aonah M., Radersburg, Montana, Case Number 977 (Box-folder 49/24)
    - Denning, James, Dubois, Idaho, Case Number 979 (Box-folder 50/1)
    - Boone, R. W., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 981 (Box-folder 50/2)
    - Lisenby, A. V., Fresno, California, Case Number 983 (Box-folder 50/3)
    - Whittier, Robert (Day-Hansen Security Company), Spokane, Washington, Case Number 997 (Box-folder 50/4)
    - Barnes, B. B., Challis, Idaho, Case Number 1010 (Box-folder 50/5)
    - Boone, R. W., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 1015 (Box-folder 50/6)
    - Kester, Bruce R., Vale, Oregon, Case Number 1016 (Box-folder 50/7)
    - Patterson, J. O., Fort Benton, Montana, Case Number 1033 (Box-folder 50/8)
    - Boone, R. W., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 1054 (Box-folder 50/9)
    - Hilger, David, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 1110 (Box-folder 50/10)
    - Pugsley, L. G., Benton Sheep Company, Case Number 1117 (Box-folder 50/11)
    - Longley and Walters, Twin Falls, Idaho, Case Number 1133 (Box-folder 50/12)
    - Call, Thomas J. and Allen, George R., Case Number 1134 (Box-folder 50/13)
    - Skillman, C. N.; Arneson, Anthony H., Case Number 1144 (Box-folder 50/14)
    - Nay and Jacobs, Grant, Montana, Case Number 1154 (Box-folder 50/15)
    - Ellsworth, Edward C., Helmville, Montana, Case Number 1158 (Box-folder 50/16)
    - Power, Charles B., Helena, Montana, Case Number 1164 (Box-folder 51/1)
    - Servis, Mrs. Aaron E., Medicine Lake, Montana, Case Number 1194 (Box-folder 51/2)
    - Chamberlain, Arthur, Avon, Montana, Case Number 1208 (Box-folder 51/3)
    - Kuhr, W. H., Chinook, Montana, Case Number 1225 (Box-folder 51/4)
    - Nelson and Moore, Havre, Montana, Case Number 1234 (Box-folder 51/5)
    - Pound, H. C., Big Timber, Montana, Case Number 1236 (Box-folder 51/6)
    - Metcalf, George, Philipsburg, Montana, Case Number 1237 (Box-folder 51/7)
    - Wick, O. T., Duluth, Minnesota, Case Number 1262 (Box-folder 51/8)
    - Maury Brothers, Lewistown, Montana, Case Number 1263 (Box-folder 51/9)
    - Moulton, C. E., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 1279 (Box-folder 51/10)
    - Bridge, J. W. and Fleming, Catherine, Helmville, Montana, Case Number 1280 (Box-folder 51/11)
    - Fricks, Martin, Lakeview, Montana, Case Number 1289 (Box-folder 51/12)
    - Barker-Wilson Company, Butte, Montana, Case Number 1298 (Box-folder 51/13)
    - Recertified Soldiers Additional, Case Number 1333 (Box-folder 51/14)
    - Holt, John M., Miles City, Montana, Case Number 1335 (Box-folder 51/15)
    - Eastern Idaho Land Company, St. Anthony, Idaho, Case Number 1336 (Box-folder 51/16)
    - Barker-Wilson Company, Butte, Montana, Case Number 1340 (Box-folder 51/17)
    - Flowerree Sheep and Horse Company, Helena, Case Number 1353 (Box-folder 51/18)
    - Curry, Arthur V., Lewishon Building, Butte, Montana, Case Number 1361 (Box-folder 51/19)
    - McIntosh, William L., Avon, Montana, Case Number 1380 (Box-folder 52/1)
    - Blair, William G., Grant, Montana and Houghton, Ivan S., Whitehall, Montana, Case Number 1383 (Box-folder 52/2)
    - Veseth, Ole, Phillips, Montana, Case Number 1401 (Box-folder 52/3)
    - Grove, Victor G., Chesaw, Washington, Case Number 1416 (Box-folder 52/4)
    - Flowerree, William K., Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 1423 (Box-folder 52/5)
    - Pickett, H. G., Helena, Montana, Case Number 1424 (Box-folder 52/6)
    - Osnes, Ole G., Square Butte, Montana, Case Number 1429 (Box-folder 52/7)
    - Garland, R. W., Malta, Montana, Case Number 1431 (Box-folder 52/8)
    - Gunn, Milton S., Helena, Montana, Case Number 1437 (Box-folder 52/9)
    - Moulton Settlers Rights, Case Number 1438 (Box-folder 52/10)
    - Morton, Elvira J., Missoula, Montana, Case Number 1439 (Box-folder 52/11)
    - Gibson, L. W., Glasgow, Montana, Case Number 1446 (Box-folder 52/12)
    - Spencer, George W., Glasgow, Montana, Case Number 1451 (Box-folder 52/13)
    - Jess, Asmus H., Glasgow, Montana, Case Number 1452 (Box-folder 52/14)